<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bully Toolkit</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string-array name="bodyTypeSpinArray">
        <item>Unfit</item>
        <item>Average</item>
        <item>Athletic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="intelligenceSpinArray">
        <item>Stupid</item>
        <item>Average</item>
        <item>Asian Smart</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="wealthSpinArray">
        <item>Poor</item>
        <item>Average</item>
        <item>Trump Status</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="heightSpinArray">
        <item>Short</item>
        <item>Middle Class</item>
        <item>Tall</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="cleanFilter">Clean Filter</string>

    <string name="clearSavedButton">Clear</string>
    <string-array name="sortArray">
        <item>Oldest - Most Recent</item>
        <item>Most Recent - Oldest</item>
        <item>Alphabetical</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="aboutMe">"My name\'s Ben and I'm a junior in college at Texas State University majoring in computer science."
        "I\'ve started learning android on my own time as I aspire to make something great and that is worthwhile in the future."
        "Wanting to create something unique, I knew I needed to be more technical from my past entreprenurial efforts of an online"
        "electronics business in High School. This is my 1st app, and it is completely free. Helping me in this endeavor is my"
        " fellow colleuge coicendentally named Ben. Anything is appreciated! Thanks for downloading my silly app"</string>

    <string name="disclaimer">"All comments, jokes, asides, rubbish, cabbages etc are of my own making and in no way represent the policy of the University of Texas State,"
        "or any other member of the University, nor any cat, dog, goldfish, insect, bacteria, mineral, etc, on campus. Any resemblance between the above views and those of "
        "my employer, my terminal, or the view out my window are purely coincidental. As I am self-employed, this *is* the opinion of my employer. Calm down -- it's only ones and zeros. "
        " These opinions are shareware. If you like them, send $10."
</string>

    <string name="savedButton">Save</string>
    <string name="generateButton">Generate</string>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>

    <string name="submitButton">Submit</string>

</resources>
